1. **We respect your privacy**
2. Brook Eden respects your right to privacy and is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers and website visitors. We adhere to the Australian Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). This policy sets out how we collect and treat your personal information. We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice or our practices with regard to your personal information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://brookeden.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
3. "Personal information" is information we hold which is identifiable as being about you.
4. **Collection of personal information**
5. Brook Eden will, from time to time, receive and store personal information you enter onto our website, provided to us directly or given to us in other forms.
6. If you purchase products through our website, we will collect your name, phone number, address, products ordered, and email address in order to fulfil your order. We will collect debit/credit card information if you choose to contact us directly for payment. If you enter payment information directly on our website, your payment data is processed by Ecwid and we do not have access to your credit card numbers or security information. You may find the Ecwid privacy notice here: [https://www.ecwid.com/privacy-policy.](https://www.ecwid.com/privacy-policy.)
7. You are able to join our Vintage Club through our website, or by contacting us directly. If you join our Vintage Club, we will collect data to enable regular wine deliveries to you. This includes your your name, phone number, address, products ordered, and email address as well as credit/debit card information.
8. If you elect to receive our newsletter we will at a minimum collect your name and email address. We will also collect other data that you may wish to optionally share with us, such as your residential address or phone number. You can unsubscribe from our marketing email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send or by contacting us direcly.
9. It is a requirement of the Tasmanian State government that you enter your data of birth in order to view wine pricing and order details. We perform an automated check on this data to ensure that you are 18 years or older. We do not collect or store your date of birth, but we do store the information that you are over 18 years of age.
10. Additionally, we may also collect any other information you provide while interacting with us. For example, through our contact form.
11. We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Website, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Website. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we may have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://brookeden.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
12. Information Automatically collected
13. In Short: Some information, such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and/or browser and device characteristics is collected automatically when you visit our Website.
14. We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Website. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Website and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Website, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.
15. We do not use Google Analytics to collect your site visit data.
16. We may also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.
17. If you interact with the Google Maps components in our website, Google will collect location data such as information about your device's location, which can be either precise or imprecise. You can opt out of allowing Google to collect this information either by refusing access to the information or by disabling your Location setting on your device. The Google privacy policy may be found at [https://policies.google.com/privacy.](https://policies.google.com/privacy)
18. **How we collect your personal information**
19. Brook Eden collects personal information from you in a variety of ways, including when you interact with us electronically or in person, when you access our website and when we provide our services to you. We may receive personal information from third parties. If we do, we will protect it as set out in this Privacy Policy.
20. Vintage Club and newsletter data that you may provide to us is stored in a secure, encrypted database. This is kept offline.
21. **Use of your personal information**
22. Brook Eden may use personal information collected from you to provide you with information, updates and our services. We may also make you aware of new and additional products, services and opportunities available to you. We may use your personal information to improve our products and services and better understand your needs.
23. Brook Eden may contact you by a variety of measures including, but not limited to telephone, email, sms or mail.
24. **Disclosure of your personal information**
25. We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy. Personal information is only supplied to a third party when it is required for the delivery of our services. If you purchase wine from us for delivery to your address, we will share your information with Australia Post. The Australia Post privacy policy may be found at [https://auspost.com.au/privacy.](https://auspost.com.au/privacy.)
26. We may from time to time need to disclose personal information to comply with a legal requirement, such as a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, warrant, in the course of a legal proceeding or in response to a law enforcement agency request.
27. We may also use your personal information to protect the copyright, trademarks, legal rights, property or safety of Brook Eden, brookeden.com.au, its customers or third parties.
28. If there is a change of control in our business or a sale or transfer of business assets, we reserve the right to transfer to the extent permissible at law our user databases, together with any personal information and non-personal information contained in those databases. This information may be disclosed to a potential purchaser under an agreement to maintain confidentiality. We would seek to only disclose information in good faith and where required by any of the above circumstances.
29. By providing us with personal information, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the types of disclosure covered by this Policy. Where we disclose your personal information to third parties, we will request that the third party follow this.
30. **Security of your personal information**
31. Brook Eden is committed to ensuring that the information you provide to us is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure information and protect it from misuse, interference, loss and unauthorised access, modification and disclosure.
32. The transmission and exchange of information is carried out at your own risk. We cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us, or receive from us. Although we take measures to safeguard against unauthorised disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personal information that we collect will not be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
33. We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements).
34. **Access to your personal information**
35. You may request details of personal information that we hold about you in accordance with the provisions of the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth). If you would like a copy of the information, which we hold about you or believe that any information we hold on you is inaccurate, out of date, incomplete, irrelevant or misleading, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://brookeden.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
36. We reserve the right to refuse to provide you with information that we hold about you, in certain circumstances set out in the Privacy Act.
37. Complaints about privacy
38. If you have any complaints about our privacy practises, please feel free to send in details of your complaints to Edward Ferrero, 167 Adams Road, Lebrina, Tasmania, 7254 or email [\[email protected\]](https://brookeden.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) We take complaints very seriously and will respond shortly after receiving written notice of your complaint.
39. **Changes to Privacy Policy**
40. Please be aware that we may change this Privacy Policy in the future. We may modify this Policy at any time, in our sole discretion and all modifications will be effective immediately upon our posting of the modifications on our website or notice board. Please check back from time to time to review our Privacy Policy.

Approved by  
Edward Ferrero  
Date: 1st September 2021

We support [Kiva](https://www.kiva.org/lender/ed7263) - loans that change lives.

### Google Reviews

**Glenn**

Apr 2024   

Nice small winery with very friendly staff. Large variety & many wines are aged including several pinot noirs.

**Adelle Rose**

Jan 2024   

Loved every wine my husband and I tried here. Will definitely be ordered some when we get back to the Gold Coast.

**Liisa Jämsä**

Dec 2023   

$10 for tasting 7 wines! Very friendly and knowledgeable host. We didn't see platypus at the lake though.

**Bernadette Murphy**

Dec 2023   

We had a fantastic cellar door experience. All the wines were excellent and the host was knowledgeable and personable. Highly recommend a stop at this vineyard.

**Brook Eden Vineyard**

167 Adams Rd  
Lebrina  
Tasmania 7254

**ABN - 89 864 913 559**

**TAS Liquor Licence #75100229**

**Phone**  
03 6395 6244

**Mobile - Ed**  
0411 525 649

**Mobile - Annette**  
0411 525 694

[\[email protected\]](https://brookeden.com.au/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**WARNING**

Under the _Liquor Licensing Act 1990_ it is an offence:

For liquor to be delivered to a person under the age of 18 years.

For a person under the age of 18 years to purchase liquor.

Search
